Jamie Joseph Heiney

Web Developer

About Me

Highly motivated web developer with experience in Javascript, Node.js, and React. Committed to creating engaging website applications while ensuring efficient code and user-friendly interfaces. Enjoys solving complex problems and staying current with new technologies.

Skills

- Javascript
- Node.js
- React
- · Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- · QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Google Sheets
- Excel
- · Cash Flow Management
- · Budgeting and Financial Planning
- · Excellent Communication
- Simplification of Complex Topics

Experience

Web Developer Intern

June 2022 - Present

- · Creating interactive website applications using Javascript, Node.js, and React
- Collaborating with senior developers to ensure efficient and optimized code
- · Working with UX/UI designers to ensure user-friendly interfaces

Accountant

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- · Managed multiple companies' bookkeeping needs, including creating chart of accounts and bank reconciliation
- · Designed and implemented a comprehensive loan tracking system using Google Sheets and Google App Scripts
- · Provided consulting services to other companies

Nursing Home Game Creator

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities
- · Managed accounts receivable and gained a broad understanding of business and management

AP Regional Manager

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017

- · Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes
- · Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts
- Acted as a liaison between corporate and nursing home accounts payable departments

Education

Certificate - Accounting Foundations Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks Online Essential Training QuickBooks Pro Essential Training

Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School

Diploma

May 2008

Dual Enrollment Florida International University

Accounting Course

Accounting Coach course by Harold Averkamp Tested and received